ADITYA BHARDWAJ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Contact

(070) 3981-6735



aditya23b@gmail.com



Tokyo, Japan



linkedin.com/in/aditya23b



Education

(Aug 2017)

Electronics & Comm. Engineering

B.V.C.O.E, New Delhi GGSIP University – Delhi, India

Programming Languages

SAP ABAP & OpenSQL

Python*

Java*

VB

SQL*

C & C++*

HTML & CSS*

Certification

JLPT N2 (July 2019)

Languages

Hindi (Native Level) English (Native Level) Japanese (Business Level)

Profile

GIT Engineer at Human Resocia, Tokyo with 5 years of experience in SAP ABAP object development for MM, SD, FI and PP modules. Possesses B.Tech in Electronics and Communication Engineering. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into a role as Software Developer.

Professional Experience

GLOBAL IT ENGINEER

Role: ABAP Developer

FEB 2019 – Present

Human Resocia – Tokyo, Japan

- Working as a contract employee in Hitachi solutions Create Ltd.'s Projects as an ABAP Developer.
- Worked on interfacing SAP system with non-SAP systems and automation of manual SAP processes.
- Worked in development of new objects from Requirement gathering phase till the Production Release and worked on post production issues.
- Trained and mentored new joiners in SAP ABAP.
- Implemented a new technique for performance enhancement called 'Parallel Processing' and achieved 50% reduction in processing time of existing programs.

ASSISTANT SYSTEM ENGINEER

DEC 2017 – JAN 2019

Role: ABAP Developer

TATA Consultancy Services Ltd, India

- Attended a 3 months training in SAP ABAP Development.
- Worked on development of ABAP objects for MM, SD and FI modules.
- Conducted Cross Module training on SAP Smartforms for SAP Functional Consultants.

Online Courses

- Udemy course 'Python for Data science and machine learning Bootcamp' completed in Dec 2022.
- Udemy course 'Complete Python Bootcamp' completed in July 2022.
- OpenSAP course 'Python for beginners' completed in Jun 2022.
- OpenSAP course 'SAP Fiori Overview Design, Develop 'completed in July 2020.
- OpenSAP course 'The Internet of Things with SAP' completed in May 2020.
- Udemy course 'SAP OO ABAP Objects with Real Time Examples and OOALV' completed in Nov 2019.

^{*:} Learnt in College / Utilised in College Project

KEY WORK PROJECTS:

Project Description	Duration	Contributions
Support and S4 migration of SAP	May 2022 -	Developing tools to help in S4 migration.
system of Manufacturing Company	Present	Analysis of existing customer code to be migrated.
VB, ASP.NET Web development Project	Jan 2022 -	Created POC prototype web apps for Bad debt management. System.
for Manufactory Company	Apr 2022	
Support and Development of SAP	Jan 2021 -	Developed Interfaces for exchange of financial information between
system of Manufacturing Company	Apr 2022	SAP and non-SAP peripheral systems.
Support and Development of SAP	Jun 2019 – Dec	Implemented a technique called Parallel processing for performance
system of Manufacturing Company	2020	improvement of existing codes and managed to reduce processing time
		by 50%.
		Developed an addon program for setting technically completed (TECO)
		Status to production orders.
		 Conducted mentoring and training of new joiners in SAP ABAP.
Support and Development for SAP	Dec 2017 - Jan	Developed a custom Procure-To-Pay cycle report for procurement
system of Real Estate Company	2019	department.
		• Developed an addon program for automation of credit memo issuance.
		Conducted Cross module training on SmartForms for functional
		Consultants

PROJECTS DONE ALONG WITH ONLINE COURSE:

Title	Description	
Analysis of movie ratings given by websites	Analysed the ratings of website 'Fandango' which sells movie tickets and compare	
which sell movie tickets	with rating of websites which don't sell movie tickets such as IMDB, MetaCritic, Rotten	
	Tomatoes.	
	Result of analysis and comparison :-	
	- Movie rating of Fandango was higher than ratings of IMDB, MetaCritic and Rotten Tomatoes	
	- The movies having rating less than 3 in IMDB, MetaCritic and Rotten Tomatoes had more than 3 rating in Fandango. There were no movies in Fandango which had a rating below 3.	
	- In fandango's movie reviews ratings were always rounded up for example: 3.6 was rounded up to 4 but even 3.1 was rounded up to 4.	
Prediction of Real Estate Prices in Tokyo	Used Kaggle dataset containing real estate prices in japan from 2005 to 2019. Used machine learning and created a model for prediction of real estate prices in Tokyo.	

PROJECTS DURING GRADUATION:

Title	Description
Lasor Based Vehicle Guidance System	This system was designed for guidance of robots using laser for carrying packages within warehouse.
Energy Efficient Smart Home System	 The system provides user with an android app for remotely controlling appliances over the internet. It has following features: - Options for automatically turning on / off appliances by detecting human presence. Location based scheduling of appliances such as turning on AC when the user is within 1 km radius from home. Monitoring of humidity, temperature etc using sensors
Railway Enquiry System	An Android App with features of reporting Live Train Status, checking PNR status,
	Trains Between Stations and Station Name to Code converter.